cleverelements.com 2011-11-23

# Imprint - Clever Elements

## Responsible for editing and content

#### Address

Clever Elements GmbH  
Prinzessinnenstraße 19-20  
D-10969 Berlin  
Germany 

**Managing Directors:**  
Manuel Kistner, Matthias Meinecke

#### Corporate data

**Registered Office:**  
Berlin  
**Register Court:**  
Amtsgericht Charlottenburg  
**Commercial Register / VAT-ID.:**  
HRB 125967 B / DE 813700499

Please note: the English version of this document is provided for informational purpose only.  
In doubt, only the German version is legally binding due to German law.  
The German version of this document can be found here.

## Disclaimer

### 1\. General

Clever Elements (Author) assumes no responsibility for the topicality, correctness, completeness or quality of information provided. Liability claims against the author relating to material or immaterial nature caused by use or disuse of the information or the use of incorrect and incomplete information are basically excluded, provided that the author is not intentional or grossly negligent present. All offers are non-binding. The author reserves itself it expressly to change parts of or the entire offer without prior notice, add to, delete or cease publication temporarily or permanently.

###  2\. Hyperlinks

For direct or indirect references to external Internet pages ("links") that lie outside the responsibility of the author, liability would only come into effect if, in which the author is aware of the contents and it is technically possible and reasonable to prevent the use of illegal content. The author therefore expressly declares that at the time of linking the linked pages contained no illegal content. The author has no influence on the current and future design and content of the linked / associated pages. He therefore distances himself explicitly from all contents all linked / connected pages which were changed after the link. This applies to all within the own Internet offer set left and references as well as for external entries in guest books, discussion forums and mailing lists. For illegal, incorrect or incomplete contents and especially for damages resulting from the use or disuse of such information lies solely with the provider of the site referred to, not the one who has linked to these pages.

### 3\. Copyright and Trademark Law

The author strives to respect the copyrights of the graphics, sound files, video sequences and texts created by himself to use graphics, sound files, video sequences and texts or to use graphics, sound files, video sequences and texts. All within the Internet offer and possibly protected brands and trademarks are the provisions of applicable trademark law and the rights of their respective owners. The mere mention does not imply that trademarks are not protected by law! The copyright for published by the author himself remains solely with the author. Any reproduction or use of graphics, sound files, video sequences and texts in other electronic or printed publications without the express permission of the author.

### 4\. Legal validity of this disclaimer notice

This disclaimer is to be regarded as part of the internet publication which you were referred to on this page. If sections or individual terms of this statement are not legal or correct, the remaining parts of the document in their content and validity.

## Privacy Policy

### 1\. General

We never share your information with third parties, but only use them in order to offer you our services. We commit ourselves explicitly as part of our membership in the [Deutschen Dialogmarketing Verband DDV](http://www.ddv.de/), by signing the [Ehrenkodex eMail-Marketing](http://www.ddv.de/) and by our certification by the [Certified Senders Alliance](http://www.certified-senders.eu/). So you can rest assured that your information is safe with us.

### 2\. What data is stored?

When registering, ordering or contacting Clever Elements you will be asked to provide us with personal information such as name, e-mail or phone number. Of course you are free not to provide this information. In this case, the Clever Elements GmbH is not always able to provide you with the requested products, services or information available.

### 3\. Technically needed data

When you visit any website to be - for technical reasons - stored information about an IP address, referring URL, date / time, browser version and operating system in the server's log files. In addition, partially so-called cookies are stored locally on your computer. Cookies are small text files that are temporarily stored on your hard drive and contain information about your visit to our website. They facilitate navigation and provide a higher degree of user friendliness. This data will be technically and in no way associated with any individual person. An evaluation is only in the form of anonymous statistics (see usage statistics).

### 4\. Usage Statistics

To further improve the offer of our site, we collect statistical data on its use. We use the services of Google Analytics. Cookies can and / or JavaScript are used. From this data is saved using an anonymous user profiles. The data will be collected and stored in anonymous form. The data are not used to personally identify a visitor personally and are not combined with information about the bearer of the pseudonym. It is thereby ensured that no link is made to the above protocol or user profile data. 

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States . Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. 

The data collection and storage can be revoked at any time with future effect. [On this website](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en), the company Google offers a free opt-out add-on. Given the debate about the use of analytical tools with full IP addresses, please be aware that this website uses Google Analytics with the "_anonymizeIp ()" is used and therefore IP addresses will be processed only shortened to exclude a direct Personenbeziehbarkeit. 

### 5\. How is personal information used?

Personal data is from Clever Elements only collected, processed and used to the extent necessary to carry out the services offered. Answers also uses this data element if necessary in addition to the purpose specified in the entry field - if you give us your consent.

### 6\. Who will be granted access to those information?

If you provide us with personal data are made available, we use it only to answer your questions, to execute contracts with you and for technical administration. Your personal information will only be passed on or otherwise transferred only if it is necessary to fulfill a contract, it is necessary for billing purposes or if you have previously agreed. You have the right to consent with effect for the future at any time.

### 7\. Deletion of stored data

Your personal data will be deleted if you withdraw your consent to storage, if their knowledge to fulfill the intended purpose of the saving is no longer necessary or if their storage is inadmissible for other legal reasons.

### 8\. Information about stored data

You can receive free information about all your personal data, Clever Element has saved about you. Of course you have the opportunity to correct any errors, outdated information in time to bring up to date or delete the stored data. You can also revoke a previously given consent to the collection, processing and use of your personal data at any time. 

Safety note: We are trying to save your personal data by taking all technical and organizational possibilities so that they are not accessible to third parties. When communicating by e-mail the complete data security can not be guaranteed, so we recommend sending confidential information by post.

### 9\. Contact for Privacy

For questions regarding the collection, processing or use of your personal information, the disclosure, correction, blocking or deletion of data and revocation of consents granted, please contact us at:

Clever Elements GmbH  
c/o Manuel Kistner  
Prinzessinnenstraße 19-20  
D-10969 Berlin  
Germany  
Phone: +49 30 60 988 295-0 

### 10\. Legal validity of this privacy notice

This privacy policy is to be regarded as part of the internet publication which you were referred from this page. If sections or individual terms of this statement are not legal or correct, the remaining parts of the document in their content and validity.
